[swanky swing music playing]
♪ Life is grand ♪
♪ Enjoy the ride ♪
♪ Until it's time… ♪
♪ Let's go in style ♪
♪ Live it up ♪
♪ Take my advice ♪
All right, drop the anchor!
♪ And when it's time to go ♪
♪ Let's go in style ♪
♪ Now, it's been… ♪
This is a perfect environment
to ponder over our new heist.
♪ Let's be together… ♪
I think I have a great idea.
I've been mulling it over lately.
Really? Pray tell.
Rob a bank. I want us to target the vault.
Not just any bank, of course.
The one with the most safety deposit boxes
in all of Spain. 7,624.
The deposit boxes are all private,
kept in a vault.
The place is quite special, actually.
People's valuables are kept secret.
Rumor has it there are jewels and gold,
but you wanna know the truth?
It's where people hide their dirty money.
So, in that case,
your plan is to rob boxes
without having any idea what's in them?
Is that it? Pretty risky surprise.
Oh, no. No surprise there.
I'm talking about the Bank of Marbella.
They've upped the number
of deposit boxes three times.
You wanna know why?
Because Marbella is
an incredibly rich city.
It's home to Russian multimillionaires
and Arab sheiks,
and all the mafias worldwide.
The Lebanese, Italians, Moroccan.
What do you think they store there?
Their grandmothers' knitting medals? No.
Lots of gold and dirty money.
Care to go for a dip?
♪ But, baby, let's go ♪
♪ In style ♪
Best time to do it is Christmas.
This year, Christmas Eve is on a Friday,
and Christmas is on a Saturday.
The bank will also be closed
on the Sunday,
so we'll have three days to get in
and clean out.
So you would like me to help you
to commit robbery on Christmas,
without knowing
what exactly we're stealing.
I just told you, it's all dirty money.
Indecent amounts of it.
Sue me if I'm wrong.
Brother, listen to me.
Can you guarantee
that there's more than 15 million euros?
I won't bother for less,
and I want it in cash.
I have no use for jewels,
and I don't want gold.
You have a better idea?
Why are we attending a social event
for millionaire yachtsmen?
The Vintage Yacht World Cup.
No, no, no, these are our fishing grounds.
Mingling with multimillionaires
is the surest way to achieve our goal.
Think about the two parts of that word.
"Multi" and "millionaires."
And so, what does it stand for?
It stands for multiple millions.
If you want to rub shoulders
with multimillionaires,
why not go to Monaco?
Oh, for heaven's sake, that's old school.
The real multimillionaires are here.
The adventurous ones.
The ones that sail
throughout the world in their yachts.
The ones we are interested in.
Care to know why?
Because they think they're just like us.
They're proud neo-hippies.
They wear T-shirts
instead of sports coats.
Like the guy who owns Facebook.
They all think they're so down-to-earth.
San Sebastián is the new Monaco.
[sultry lounge cover
of "I Want to Break Free" playing]
♪ I want to break free ♪
♪ I want to break free… ♪
- Thank you.
- Of course.
[Damián] How will we choose who to rob?
That's actually
one of my favorite parts of our craft.
The seduction.
It's not enough just
to target someone with a large fortune.
You have to earn their trust as well.
It's crucial to get
into their circle of friends.
Into their private life.
And from that vantage point,
find out how they manage
their fortune and where they entrust it.
Before they know it,
you take what's theirs.
They're like lambs
out to slaughter. [chuckles]
Now I understand why we're here.
To seduce.
Shall we begin?
Uh, madam, good evening. Excuse me.
My colleague and I were noticing
your stunning dress.
You look absolutely marvelous.
Thank you.
That's very kind. My name is Margarita.
- Nice to meet you.
- And you are?
Ricardo Pérez Infante.
He owns a shipping company
in North Africa.
But we interrupted you, forgive us.
I'm going to go admire the boats now.
- [under breath] What are you doing?
- [Margarita] I own a shipping company.
- Really?
- [Margarita] But elsewhere.
[Damián] What a coincidence. [chuckles]
[Margarita] Yes.
[gasps]
My necklace.
[Berlin] Ah.
Careful. Uh, may I?
[bright music rises]
Please, allow me.
[chuckles] Thanks. Just a second.
Let me see.
[both chuckle]
There. I think I got all the pearls.
Thanks a lot.
I noticed it felt
a little loose when I fastened it earlier.
Mm. Ah.
May I have the honor? Great.
Careful with your hair. There.
You know, jewelry clasps don't always have
the same quality.
Since they're not the same quality
as the rest, they expand and loosen.
Wow. You're quite the expert in jewelry.
No. Just an enthusiast.
My grandfather was a jeweler. In Paris.
And you? You're…?
Ah. My name's Simón. Charmed.
Dare I say I know who you are,
Genoveva Dante, Duchess of Málaga.
What a pleasure.
- Enchanted.
- Feeling's mutual.
Excuse me. Lady Genoveva,
your car is ready for you.
Sorry to leave.
I'd love to continue our conversation,
but I have other engagements, sadly.
May I walk you out?
I'd love that.
You know this venue is one
of the best I've seen for a party.
[both chuckle]
That's right. Yes.
[laughs warmly]
What a shame
you can't stay longer this evening.
But I assure you,
you've made this party unforgettable.
- Will I see you at dinner?
- I'm off to Seville now.
Ah, right. I understand perfectly.
Your residence there is
one of the most striking in town.
Sounds like you've seen my palace.
Suffice it to say that every time
I pass by it, I'm intrigued.
I can't help admiring the façade.
I imagine it's
an architectural gem inside.
How would you like to see it?
I'd love that.
And if you host my visit,
it'll be double the pleasure.
How about next week, then?
How about two weeks from now?
I've been traveling strictly in my yacht,
and it takes longer, naturally.
I'll wait for you.
[sultry, intriguing music playing]
Tell me about the lady I left you with.
How'd it go?
Did her dentures
fall in her gin and tonic?
[Damián] That's classy.
Who is she?
The millionaire I want us to rob.
[flamenco-inspired theme song playing]
[vibrant flamenco music playing]
- [music ends abruptly]
- [bells tolling the hour]
[whimsical music playing]
[dogs growl]
[chuckles]
[elegant piano music playing]
Duchess, a treat for you.
- You shouldn't have.
- Nonsense. It was my pleasure.
Come with me now.
You don't know
how thrilled I am that you're here.
[Berlin chuckles]
- Are you taking me on a tour?
- [laughs]
No, later.
I'll tell you
all about its glorious history,
but first things first,
there's something more pressing.
- There is? What is it?
- It's a surprise.
- You'll see. Right through here.
- Mm.
What a delight.
I'm thrilled you accepted my invitation.
[sighs]
[elegant music peaks, fades]
I've been looking forward to this moment.
My wife told me you are quite the admirer
of the architecture in Seville
and of my home in particular.
[chuckles] Yes, in passing.
I've always admired the elegant Neo-Gothic
and Neo-Mudéjar styles.
That's not all.
I'll show you the wing
that's Neo-Renaissance.
A complimentary art history class.
If you'll excuse me, I'll make sure
the chocolates are put in the fridge.
- They'll melt in this heat.
- Thank you, my love. [kisses]
[chuckles slightly]
[duke] Shall we sit?
I'd love that.
I said I was really looking forward
to this moment
because I've been wanting to meet you.
I've heard great things about you.
Great things, truly.
- Mind if I ask who spoke about me?
- Hm.
[scoffs]
[dramatic music rises]
[chuckles]
[duke] You are a brilliant man.
I'd go so far as to say
that you're… a genius.
I admire your talent.
Your career is second to none.
No slip-ups.
And you never leave any evidence
at all for the police to find.
What's this about, sir?
Is this a veiled threat?
No, no, no, not at all.
You misunderstood me.
I have no intention of blackmailing you
or asking you where the chalice is.
It actually belongs
to a good friend of mine,
but he's accepted his loss.
Hm. So you see, I'm genuinely
impressed with what you do.
That's why I wanted to have you over.
I have an offer for you.
I'd like you to bring me something.
An original Leonardo da Vinci.
The Lady with an Ermine.
Have you heard of it?
It's one of a series of four portraits
of women he painted.
The original piece is in Kraków,
at the Czartoryski Museum.
How marvelous.
See? A true expert. Exactly.
But it's coming to Seville
as part of an exhibition
on the Renaissance.
It's going to be shown
at the former convent Merced Calzada.
Right, known today
as the Museum of Fine Arts.
Don't you think it's magical?
A delightful twist of fate. [gasps]
The masterpiece is coming here.
[sighs] I've dreamed of this.
He's dreamed of this.
That's what that bozo said.
He admires what I do
as if I were the pope.
- Who are you talking about?
- The duke of Málaga ambushed me.
Inviting me to his palace
was just a front.
He lured me with his wife.
She's beautiful, right?
She told him all about me.
He knows I'm a ladies' man,
and I would never have the heart
to reject her.
What was the point? What does he want?
He showed me a picture
of the chalice we stole in Madrid.
[dog barking and growling]
Where did he get the picture?
Where did he get that information?
What does that matter to us now, Damián?
The only thing that matters now
is that he wants me to steal for him.
He thinks I'm some pawn
who works for others?
Do I look like a henchman,
or I depend on commissions?
Do I look like an errand boy?
You know the truth?
My robberies are works of art,
masterpieces.
I don't follow the whims of an amateur.
I get it. So you told him
you can't accept his request?
Not exactly, no.
- You agreed to it?
- No, I did not, all right?
I told him I'd think about it.
God, the heat in Seville is unbearable!
[Damián] But…
Why didn't you flat-out refuse?
Because I want to teach him a lesson.
That's why. I'm going to make him pay
for treating me this way.
Hang on, Andrés.
How do you expect to make him pay? Huh?
Haven't you heard the saying,
"It's no crime to steal from a thief?"
Well, I want to claim what's his.
That's right.
We're looking for our next target.
That harebrained millionaire is perfect.
He's more of a criminal than we are.
He won't be able to rat on us.
Andrés, I think you're overreacting.
No, I'm not. That guy knows who we are.
He knows who you are.
If we turn him down,
it could backfire on us.
We have to say yes. He's our next heist.
And he'll have to live with that.
Yes or no?
[chuckles] Call the others.
[couple arguing indistinctly nearby]
[passionate flamenco guitar music rises]
[crowd murmuring]
[woman shouting]
Here, take your goddamn records!
I want you out of my house!
Candela, you're losing your mind!
You think I'm losing my mind?
Wait till you see how I am when I go down!
Didn't I tell you to leave?
Why don't you do what I ask you to?
- Please, just tell me what I did.
- You and your cousin had an affair.
Candela, Jesus!
I swear nothing happened with her.
- You need to leave. Get out.
- I don't even know how to tell you--
[passionate music fades]
[sniffles]
Why are you looking at me like that?
Want a picture?
No reason.
[scoffs] "No reason." Yeah, right.
I was just counting my blessings.
I'm glad I'm not that man.
But you look like you're about to faint.
Like a horse who worked all day.
I know. My suit's 100% linen,
but I'm still sweltering.
I don't know how you do it.
It's 115 degrees
in the shade in this city. It's awful.
I'll tell you how.
We're all fiery around here.
We're all very hot-blooded.
It boils in seconds. It's in our nature.
- The city's as torrid as we are.
- Yes, I see that.
But you've never considered
moving to Switzerland or something?
[laughs] Switzerland… Yeah, right.
Here. I want you to have this album.
You look like you know good music.
For the record,
life's pretty good in the South.
- We've got… flamenco.
- Mm…
The Guadalquivir.
- Orange trees everywhere…
- Ah.
And over 300 statues of Sevillian virgins.
- And the Passion.
[both chuckle]
And forgive me,
but after seeing that heated argument,
it's fair to say that most people
will never feel such unfiltered emotions
in their entire lives.
Well, we just don't beat
around the bush here.
We charge at full speed, you know?
[both laugh]
No, no, no, no.
I think it's more like full force.
- [tsks] No. How would you know?
- I know I'm right.
It's natural for you to be strong.
It's too hot to be quick.
- [laughs]
- Whatever.
I want you to have these
so when you listen,
you'll remember me.
- You'll never forget me, you'll see.
- Thank you.
I have a piece of advice for you.
I think that the easiest way for you
to avoid suffering from this heat here
is to not wear a silly jacket.
Farewell.
- [scoffs]
- Uh, can I help you?
- No, no, it's fine.
- Are you sure?
Hm.
I got a hold of the others.
They'll be here in 48 hours.
- That's great.
- What's with the records?
That woman stole my wallet
with so much finesse,
she'd put David Copperfield to shame.
She gave me a couple records,
chatted me up,
and pushed me ever so slightly
to create a diversion not once, but twice.
She managed to check both my pant pockets
and took it effortlessly.
It levitated. [laughs]
Never touched me. A true expert.
And… what was in it?
Nothing, really. 600 or 700 euros.
Hey. Theft with prestidigitation
is an art form.
- Sure. Sure.
- I am more than happy to pay for it.
Naturally…
What do you mean?
It's either that or you're looking forward
to getting your wallet back. Huh?
[chuckling]
[suspenseful music playing]
[Berlin] After the heist in Paris,
Bruce was both enchanted
and confused by Keila.
She was the 34th woman
he'd kissed in his life.
And she ignited desires in him
he'd never felt before with anyone else.
He loved waiting for her
at the hairdresser's.
Or going to the movies with her,
not knowing what he was going to see.
And one day, while looking at
a Christmas display in a store window…
Keila…
…he said something he'd never said before.
Want to move in together?
[gasps]
[squeals]
Yes! [giggles]
Two weeks into living with her,
he noticed he had absolutely
no intention of running away.
Bruce realized he was deeply
in love with her.
- [snoring]
- And the old Bruce was gone.
He even threw a goodbye party
for his old self.
- [crowd clamoring]
- ["I Know You Want Me" blasting]
♪ I know you want me ♪
♪ You know I want you… ♪
[guests cheering]
[Berlin] He invited his friends,
his family, and people from his hometown.
Over 1,500 people attended.
During the big bash,
Bruce bid farewell
to the party animal inside him.
He said goodbye to alcohol, reggaeton,
and one-night stands.
♪ You know I want you ♪
[house rendition
of "Sarà perché ti amo" playing]
[Berlin] The two appeared as the bride
and groom on a wedding cake.
He stood proudly by her side.
He was thrilled to declare to everyone
how committed he was to Keila.
[both exclaim]
[both cheering]
[upbeat dance music intensifies]
[Berlin] But as Bruce was turning his back
on his wild life,
Keila, quite paradoxically,
was being seduced by it.
- [music distorts]
- [heart thumping]
[Berlin] Sometimes, a random encounter
can drag you straight
to the depths of hell.
- [dance music fades]
- [moody rock music playing]
[Berlin] Roi also got
to discover life in a relationship.
But unlike Bruce and Keila,
his experience was epic
right from the start.
[romantic rock music playing]
They first lived in a secluded cabin,
cut off from the rest of the world
like a couple of Robinson Crusoes.
Some nights, they would set up
a mattress outside
to gaze at the shooting stars together.
They'd even sleep out there on occasion.
They were so happy.
Cameron would say that when you're happy,
you can sleep pretty much anywhere.
Eventually, they grew bored
of the countryside,
so they drove into the city.
They lived wherever they wanted to,
however they wanted to.
But something must have gone wrong
along the way.
They showed up separately,
and none of us saw them speaking
to each other.
[somber music playing]
[Berlin] Everyone had their love story,
including me.
But mine was more of
a… bromance with Damián.
When the adrenaline
of the Paris heist wore off,
Damián returned to an empty house
to face his loneliness.
He obsessively tried to avoid his fate
by all means possible.
So he taught longer classes…
[bell rings]
…and extended his tutorials.
He even signed up
for the teachers' padel ball league.
[grunts]
But try as he would,
there was always that moment
when the university shut off its lights.
I had bought a suitcase
and a one-way ticket
to Singapore to meet with Camille.
But I kept seeing this guy
lurking by my house every night.
He'd even double-park in the street
when he couldn't find a spot,
and when he'd see me go by,
he'd pretend to bump into me.
My man, Andrés! What a coincidence, huh?
I was on my way to the supermarket.
The one at the university's closed now.
You wanna grab a beer?
Or… catch a movie? We could go for Korean.
I came to realize
my friend desperately needed me
to take him on a trip
to get his sob story off his chest.
- And it worked.
- [energetic music playing]
[Berlin] He told me
all about it in Vancouver.
In Arizona.
In Tulum.
He continued to tell me about it
in Medellín, in Rio de Janeiro…
He didn't get off the topic for a second
during our trip
until we got to Argentina.
[music cuts out]
[Berlin] There, in Patagonia,
in front of a spectacular glacier,
crumbling to pieces
into the sea, much like his life,
he understood it was time
to pick up the pieces.
How about we go home?
[whimsical music playing]
[music fades]
[Berlin] Okay, now
that we have all the details,
we can begin. [sighs]
I assume you're all wondering
why we're here in Seville.
We've been hired to steal this portrait.
The Lady with an Ermine,
painted by Leonardo da Vinci in 1489.
It's estimated to be worth
over 300 million euros.
It's currently at the Czartoryski Museum
in Kraków.
In ten days, it'll be shipped
over here, to Seville, for an expo.
But! We're not going to do it.
Allow me.
For now, our main focus is not going
to be what we steal,
but from whom.
Álvaro Hermoso de Medina
is the person who wants us to carry out
this disgraceful task, and, um…
Back to you.
This man is the heir
of a lineage of Spanish nobles,
and he lives in one
of the prestigious palaces in Seville.
The property spreads
over 8,000 square meters.
There are cloisters,
gardens, stables, even a church.
As far as we know, he has a cellar filled
with world-famous sherry.
There's a ranch to breed fighting bulls.
When it comes to bullfighting,
he's a virtuoso.
But why would an aristocrat
from such a noble lineage,
with a palace and all,
want a stolen piece of art?
I asked him the exact same question.
The Lady with an Ermine
is an alluring painting
because it's gorgeous,
but… it's also worth
a tremendous amount of money.
It's priceless, really. Is it for you or…?
Or would you like
to trade it on the black market?
[chuckles]
[both laugh]
Well, I don't think
that's any of your business.
Let's just say that I want it for myself.
As the Holy Grail of my collection.
Understood.
I would love to see it.
Well, surely you'll understand
that for reasons of… security
or rather, for a logical reason,
I'd rather not show
a professional like you its location.
That collection is what we're going after.
- What's in it?
- What do you mean?
[scoffs]
The collection.
We don't know for the moment.
[laughing]
Are you fucking kidding me right now?
You're against robbing the vault
of the Bank of Marbella
because we don't know what's in there,
but you want us to steal
a mystery collection.
It makes no sense at all.
For all we know, it's a stamp collection.
Or he collects tons of coins
from around the world.
Or it's… amphorae.
Amphorae!
No one requesting
one of da Vinci's masterpieces
would store it with lesser pieces.
If it's the cherry, imagine the damn cake.
I have a feeling that the collection
is a real treasure. It's extraordinary.
The treasure that brought you here
to Seville is that jewel of a duchess.
I saw you with her in San Sebastián.
You were flirting and giggling with her
on the stairs.
You made us take a boat
all the way from the Cantabrian coast,
through the Atlantic to Seville,
for the promise of a date with her.
I think what's really going on here
is you're pissed off she lured you here
just to meet her husband.
Robberies require surgical precision.
Not the rage of a scorned man
who wants to screw over a duke.
You want to put us at risk
for a plan you haven't thought out at all,
out of ego and your arrogance.
- [Berlin] And you? Huh?
- [Damián] What?
You want to share with them
what you thought of?
He wants to dig a hole, hmm?
And make me go through it to steal safes.
With a plumber's blowtorch,
and you want it to happen over Christmas,
all because you have no one
to enjoy the holidays with.
Okay, hang on. How about this?
Whoever wants to help our friend Damián
with his plan can go ahead
and get off this boat right now.
Please get your things and leave.
And whoever wants to find out
what exactly is in the duke's collection
can stay here.
[chuckles]
[Damián] Very well, then.
I'm going to stay as well, hm?
We'll steal that collection together.
And then whoever wants to join me
can take part in the bank heist.
That way,
we'll find out whose plan was better.
[Berlin] Hm.
- [mysterious music playing]
- [Berlin] Wow. This city is stunning.
Even more so at night,
when all is quiet
and the suffocating heat lets up.
The scent of orange blossom
still perfumes the air.
Breathe it in, Roi. You'll see.
[sniffs] Smell that?
- Yeah, I do.
- Truly lovely.
Sir? Where are we going?
I need to see
if you've lost your abilities
over the past few months.
Open that door, please.
Do it.
[metallic clicking]
- Fantastic.
- [sighs]
[softly] This one as well.
Sir, this is linked
to that collection, am I right?
What collection?
- Y'know, the duke's.
- Somewhat tangentially, maybe.
Go on, go on.
[whimsical music playing]
[gasps]
How marvelous.
I've got it from here.
It's best if you go join
your other colleagues
out on the ship, all right?
[whimsical music ends]
[tense music playing]
[intriguing Spanish guitar music playing]
[soft squeaking]
[shotgun cocks]
- [suspenseful music playing]
- [groans]
- [music cuts out]
- [exhales]
[tense music rises]
[Candela] Psst.
- [Berlin exhales]
- [music fades]
[groans]
- You shot me. That's harsh.
- Don't worry. They're pellets.
It's just my cousin's BB gun.
[sighs]
- [laughs]
- Why are you in my house?
I'm here to reclaim my wallet.
[scoffs] You should've rung the doorbell
like everyone else.
Next time, I'll aim for one of your eyes.
[Spanish guitar music rises]
[music fades]
Damián, I think I've got something.
I just pulled all the duke's tax returns,
and he has three main companies.
The cattle ranch, Hermoso wineries,
and a boat rental service.
He's got a…
bunch of luxury charter yachts.
They're high-end.
Like, if you're not loaded, forget it.
- Is this useful?
- I have no idea, Cameron.
The fact he rents yachts
to the A-class doesn't lead me to believe
he's hiding
some enigmatic treasure of a collection.
I feel like a substitute teacher
right now. You know?
The language teacher stuck replacing
the physics teacher on sick leave.
This isn't even the heist I had in mind.
So… looks like I just found something.
Come see if you want.
I hacked into his emails, messages,
invoices, bank accounts,
purchases, orders…
Great, you found out
all that duke's dirty secrets.
In '99, the duke had
some very strange work done
on his country estate,
about 40 kilometers outside of Seville.
A sort of tunnel
from his house to the wineries.
So there's a train
that goes from his mansion to the cellars,
without leaving his house to board it.
A little weird, no?
Mm-hmm.
That's not the only weird thing.
In 2000, just one year later,
the duke moved everything from that winery
to the one he has in Jerez de la Frontera.
Closed the one on the estate.
I think it's fishy to have a train
that commutes to a closed business.
In his 2000 tax return,
he had a million-euro bill deducted.
From Nitax Private Security,
a security company based out of Geneva.
It's made out to the estate's address.
The company in charge of security
at Sotheby's and the Louvre.
There's a mention on their website.
[scoffs]
And why would anyone invest
to that extent to protect an empty winery?
Complete with a train
that leads directly to his own mansion?
If the duke has a collection
of great value, it's definitely there.
As you were, everyone.
Where's Berlin?
I just want to go back to my cabin.
He can take over
and lead his own investigation.
Yup. Um, we went out for a walk
around Seville for a while.
- Ah.
- Just walking around.
- Walking around. Sure.
- Mm, yeah. He stayed out is all.
Tell me, did you happen to take a stroll
at the Patio de Banderas Square?
- [scoffs] Yes.
- Number 22?
- Yeah.
- First floor, right?
- Yes.
- Oh, fuck me.
First, a treasure
leading to the collection.
Now he chases a woman
who throws records out her window.
I'm gonna call it a night.
[whimsical music playing]
[Roi sighs]
- [music fades]
- [Berlin groaning]
Mm… It's painful.
I know.
[blows]
- [Pomelo squeaks]
- [sighs]
Could you… get this charming little fellow
out of the bed for a moment?
Why would I do that?
Bunnies aren't exactly hygienic
in such circumstances.
My Pomelo is a very clean bunny.
- Ow!
- He's a vulnerable animal.
Cries a lot. Breaks my heart. All right.
Let's do the other.
Careful, please. [groans]
- [sighs]
- I got it.
So tell me, is this how you welcome men
to your home? With gunfire?
Thing is, you weren't invited.
Besides, I thought you were someone else.
- Yeah?
- My boyfriend.
My former… boyfriend.
He broke in to steal a shoebox
that had 6,000 euros in it.
He also knew I kept
all my savings in a cookie jar.
But he didn't get his hands on it.
I thought he was back
to try to take it again.
Okay, mystery solved.
Listen, if you return my wallet,
I could take you out to dinner.
Or… how about breakfast? Much better.
- Well, that's not possible.
- Why not?
- Because your wallet was in the shoebox.
- Hm.
But you know what?
Since he managed
to steal your wallet and my money too,
you're gonna come with me to get it back.
- Sound good to you?
- All right, if you insist on it.
Here, you can wear my boyfriend's T-shirt.
Me, wear a T-shirt? No.
Impossible.
[sighs]
- Have any children?
- Me? No.
Hungry? You want a chocolate bar
or something?
No, thanks. All good.
Saving my appetite for breakfast.
'Kay.
[intriguing Spanish guitar music playing]
That's it.
All right, we're good to go.
["Con dos camas vacías" playing on radio]
Oh, one of my faves.
[energetic flamenco music continues]
[in Spanish] ♪ I don't embroider
Handkerchiefs ♪
♪ You don't tear contracts ♪
♪ I don't kill out of jealousy
You don't die for me ♪
♪ And before you love me
Like one loves a cat ♪
♪ I take up with anyone
Who reminds me of you ♪
♪ I leave my doors wide open… ♪
- [in English] We'll pull over there.
- I'll go wherever you go, dear.
[in Spanish] ♪ The peace you've chosen ♪
♪ Is worse than my war ♪
♪ What could have been
And what will never be ♪
♪ I never knew how to go with the wind ♪
♪ Which bites the corners
Of this ungodly city ♪
♪ Poor sorcerer's apprentice
Spitting into the firmament… ♪
- [in English] Shall we?
- Uh-huh.
[passionate flamenco song ends]
Can I help you?
- Enjoy your meal.
- [woman] Thanks, Candela.
You won't know what hit you.
Time to have some fun with you.
Hey, where's my money?
You want me to believe you're not there?
You're tucked into bed?
How about we wake you up, then?
What? You sleeping?
Time to wake up, dear.
Maybe this will wake you up.
[neighbors complaining]
[intense Spanish guitar music playing]
[chuckles]
[ex knocking] What are you doing, Candela?
Open the door! Open it!
Candela! Candela, you're gonna kill me!
Open up!
The tank's gonna explode. Come on!
I need that shoebox you stole
from me before anything else.
[ex] What?! I didn't steal anything!
Oh, yeah, sure you didn't.
You never do anything wrong.
Like you never cheated with your cousin!
[ex] Candela, I swear to you,
nothing happened with my cousin.
I swear on my life!
- Yeah.
- [ex] Open up!
All right, take a step back, and I will!
Hey! You better stay out of this, okay?
Get away!
This concerns only us. Get closer.
Stick your head out
and swear to me you didn't sleep with her!
- I swear to you! Open the door, fuck!
- You're full of shit.
I saw how you were looking
at your cousin, all right?
You're denying it like a Judas.
"She's like my sister.
Don't worry. I grew up with her."
But you liked it when she got on your bike
and rubbed her tits on you, huh?
And going to the pool with her, right?
She'd get up on your shoulders,
and her pussy would cradle
your neck for all to see!
Get your head outta there
and look at me! Now!
It's about to explode, for fuck's sake!
Oh, please!
Stop saying it's gonna explode!
I'm not done yet.
What about shopping
for her wedding dress with her?
Who does that?
She could've gone with her mom,
her sister, or a friend… Huh?
Why go with you? It makes no sense.
What do you think you're doing
with that hose?
- Please, help me!
- Get any closer, and I'll hit you!
- Candela, this is insane! Why do this?
- How is this insane?
- Stay away!
- You're gonna regret this!
No! I never have any regrets.
- Candela!
- Move away! Fuck off!
- Candela! Please, stop.
- Listen!
All of you listen.
Nothing is going on here, okay?
Calm down.
This will all be over really soon.
Don't get any closer with that water.
And you!
- [ex] Come on, please!
- What's wrong?
You couldn't resist her
in that white dress.
[ex coughs]
- Come out. I can't see you.
- Candela, please stop. I'm begging you.
Did you fuck her that day? Tell me.
Did you fuck her that day, yes or no?
All right. I did.
But just that one time, Candela.
I was completely in love with you.
For real.
Sorry I hurt you.
I'm so sorry. I'm sorry!
That makes two of us.
[ex] Candela!
Candela!
All right, show's over now.
[neighbors clamoring]
- [ex] Candela!
- [intense rock music playing]
- [nostalgic indie tune playing]
- ♪ I'm a tattoo wish on a star… ♪
- You all right?
- Yeah.
I'm doing great.
I'm glad I turned my back on that crap.
You must think
I'm a raging lunatic, right?
Why? For shooting me in the chest
or for setting the RV on fire?
[both laugh]
We sorta had fun through it, though.
I mean, even Pomelo thinks you're great.
Okay, it was a little much
to pour gasoline on the RV like that.
Not at all. I thought you showed courage.
Really?
[sighs]
Love should end with the same force
as when you fell into it.
People wither away with long farewells.
A lot of them spend months, or even years,
trying to muster up the courage
to part ways
and… sometimes they never get around
to doing it.
That's really sad.
It's actually making me angry.
Few things are more tragic
than understanding
that your love story is over.
That it's slowly wasting away.
And resorting to excuses like having
a headache to avoid touching each other.
Or even worse,
you pretend everything's all right
until one morning,
three years down the road,
you just can't do it anymore,
and you say it.
Then the separation begins.
You put all of the other's belongings
in perfectly packed boxes…
I don't do that.
I'm more of a "throw their shit
out the window" kind of girl.
I get it, if you come into someone's life
by flinging the door wide open,
odds are, you're gonna slam it shut
when you leave.
[exhales shakily]
[sirens approaching]
Well, here we are.
That T-shirt would have come in handy.
Hang on. I'll help you.
Just take it easy.
[tense music playing]
Good evening, officer.
Good evening. Where you coming from?
We went to visit
with a friend in San Roque.
Your car smells like gasoline.
Probably 'cause I just filled the tank.
Shut off the engine.
License and registration
of the vehicle, please.
Certainly. One moment.
Simón, love. Give me the papers
from the glove compartment?
[officer] I also need
your driver's license, ma'am.
Oh, it's a mess in here.
I'm having trouble finding it.
It's always utter chaos in my purse.
Man, this is really packed.
I can't find anything for the life of me.
Too much stuff.
I'll get it for you. Just a sec.
Stay in the vehicle.
Why did all this have to happen tonight?
What's going on?
I've got a blue sedan,
license plate SE 0212 DB…
Here's your wallet.
What? I still had it in here.
I forgot to take it out.
I'm giving it back
in case they ask for your ID too.
They probably will.
And… why do you think
they'll feel the need to check mine?
I don't have a license,
and this car's not mine.
And by that, I mean it's stolen.
Mm, yeah. I kind of figured that out,
seeing as you hot-wired the car
to start it.
- Looks like we've been sandwiched.
- What?
Wonderful. Great, my God.
If they catch me again with a stolen car,
they'll lock me up for four years.
But if I run, I'll risk six.
What do you recommend?
- A bird in the hand or two in the bush?
- I've got you.
What are you doing?
Let's switch places.
Two in the bush, huh?
[dispatch] The license plate matches
a stolen vehicle report.
The car is stolen.
I repeat, the car is stolen.
[engine turns over]
Rock and roll.
[engine revs]
[energetic rock music playing]